<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

    <channel>
        <title>Quarkus</title>
        <link>https://quarkus.io</link>
        <description>Quarkus: Supersonic Subatomic Java</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 03:09:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 2.3.0.Final released - Dev Service for Neo4J, Logging with Panache, Testing CLI applications and much more</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-3-0-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                Today, we release Quarkus 2.3.0.Final which includes a lot of refinements and improvements and some new features: Dev Service for Neo4J Logging with Panache Testing support for CLI applications MongoDB Liquibase extension Support for Hibernate ORM interceptors Migration Guide To migrate from 2.2, please refer to our migration guide. What&#8217;s...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-3-0-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Alexey Loubyansky (https://twitter.com/aloubyansky)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Unused Beans and Why We Remove Them</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/unused-beans/
            </link>
            <description>
                Quarkus is a build-time oriented stack, i.e. it tries to do as much as possible at build time to improve the startup time and memory usage of your application. However, it&#8217;s not always so easy and straightforward as many existing frameworks and libraries do not take this design choice into...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/unused-beans/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Martin Kouba (https://twitter.com/martunek)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>How Quarkus Improved Logicdrop&amp;#8217;s Developer Experience and Process</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/logicdrop-customer-story/
            </link>
            <description>
                Logicdrop provides a business automation and data intelligence platform that enables enterprises to design their own solutions and run them in the cloud. We process millions of transactions a month across a global client-base and add significant value to mission-critical processes. The developer experience plays an important a role in...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/logicdrop-customer-story/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>KimJohn Quinn (https://twitter.com/logicdrop)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Eclipse Adoptium Uses Quarkus for high volume Java SE distribution API</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/adoptium-customer-story/
            </link>
            <description>
                Java is used by millions of developers worldwide and according to Redmonk, recently moved back to the #2 most used programming language. There are many distributions of the Java runtime and development kit, but the Eclipse Temurin (formerly known as AdoptOpenJDK) distribution has proven to be the most popular. Recently,...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/adoptium-customer-story/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>James Falkner (https://twitter.com/schtool)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus Newsletter #12</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-newsletter-12/
            </link>
            <description>
                The September Newsletter has been published! This month, check out great articles about Eric Deandrea&#8217;s new book "Quarkus for Spring Developers", RESTEasy reactive, and the use of "Quarkus Security OPENID Connect Multi Tenacy". Check out Newsletter #12! Want to get newsletters in your inbox? Sign up for the newsletter using...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-newsletter-12/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>James Cobb (https://twitter.com/insectengine)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>VCStream: a new messaging platform for DECATHLON’s Value Chain, built on Quarkus.</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/decathlon-user-story/
            </link>
            <description>
                DECATHLON is a French retailer, dedicated to sport products, with more than 1800 stores worldwide. At DECATHLON, we are convinced that sport is a source of well-being. VCStream is a new platform for streaming data across the Value Chain of DECATHLON. It allows streaming data in and out of the...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/decathlon-user-story/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Loïc Mathieu (https://twitter.com/loicmathieu)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 2.2.3.Final released - Maintenance release</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-2-3-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                Today, we released Quarkus 2.2.3.Final, a maintenance release for our 2.2 release train containing a few bugfixes and platform version bumps. It is a safe upgrade for anyone already using 2.2. If you are not using 2.2 already, please refer to the 2.2 migration guide. Full changelog You can get...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-2-3-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Georgios Andrianakis (https://twitter.com/geoand86)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 2.2.2.Final released - Maintenance release</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-2-2-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                Today, we released Quarkus 2.2.2.Final, a maintenance release for our 2.2 release train containing bugfixes and documentation improvements. It is a safe upgrade for anyone already using 2.2. If you are not using 2.2 already, please refer to the 2.2 migration guide. Full changelog You can get the full changelog...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-2-2-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>An Extension for Long Running Activities</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/using-lra/
            </link>
            <description>
                Introduction The Quarkus LRA extension is useful for building JAX-RS services that wish to definitively agree when an interaction has finished, with either a successful outcome or an unsuccessful one. In the successful case, all participants can clean up in the knowledge that all other services will do so as...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/using-lra/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Michael Musgrove</author>
            
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Quarkus 2.2.1.Final released - Hardening release</title>
            <link>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-2-1-final-released/
            </link>
            <description>
                Today we announce the availability of Quarkus 2.2.1.Final, which is the result of our first hardening cycle. Indeed, for 2.2, we decided to slow down on adding new features and focus this release cycle on hardening Quarkus with 3 main focuses: Fix issues Improve usability Improve documentation Thus the list...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://quarkus.io/blog/quarkus-2-2-1-final-released/
            </guid>
            
            
            
            <author>Guillaume Smet (https://twitter.com/gsmet_)</author>
            
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
